

AADIDEV AAHAN

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Fast working and friendly Blockchain developer with 5+ years of experience working on Ideal Creators Team.

Skilled in Frontend and Backend development, Defi & Dapp, NFT, Crypto, Game development, Mobile Apps development and Website development.

CONTACT

- 13 Lodhi Road St., New Delhi City

EDUCATION HISTORY

University of Delhi 2010-2015

Master in Computer science

WORK EXPERIENCE

NFT projects

2010-2014

 My small team and I build NFT marketplaces, deploy smart contracts, create NFT website, NFT staking platform and develop game on blockchains for small to medium size businesses.

Blockchain & Crypto Projects

2016-2018

 As a Blockchain developer, I specialized in custom cryptocurrency and blockchain development. I have many experience in creating Crypto exchange website, Crypto wallet app, Mobila Apps & Smart Contracts, Game development, Website developments, Defi & dApps projects and so on.

Front-end & Back-end development 2018-present

I'm Front-end Developer and UX/UI Design. I have experience on Javascript, React, NextJs, HTML, c++, CSS, Python & Solidity.
I'm also seasoned software engineer with industry experience in core back-end development in a renowned cybersecurity firm and having a post-graduate degree in Mathematics and Computer science from one of the best colleges in India.

SKILLS

NFT projects

Blockchain & Crypto projects

Front-end & Back-end development projects